# Berkan Chelikhan

+44 7960678570 🔀 berkan.c@hotmail.com 🌐 www.berkan.co.uk 🕡 github.com/berkan1

## **Profile**

A creative and diligent frontend developer with excellent problem solving and technical skills. Over 3 years of professional experience using modern technologies to create performant web applications using JavaScript frameworks with a deep understanding of the React ecosystem.

# **Experience**

#### Frontend Developer - Everledger

03/2021 - Present

- Building the frontend layer of a new mobile-first product to visualise provenance data from innovative blockchain and NFC technology using React and NextJS, working closely with the product owner, UX designers and QA engineers.
- Creating and maintaining components in the Storybook component library used across all Everledger products as well as working on microservices using NestJS when needed.

### **Software Consultant - Netcompany**

08/2019 - 03/2021

- · Part of the applications development team working on building and refining front end features and business logic for a large scale web application, using technologies such as C#, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS and Azure Logic Apps.
- Working in agile sprints following iterative and test-driven development methodologies, having also been a team lead for a scrum team of 7 software developers.

#### Trainee Computer Scientist - Royal Surrey County Hospital 09/2017 - 09/2018

- Created bespoke, in-house web applications for the Nuclear Medicine department, for which I was the sole developer.
- Worked closely with medical physicists to create numerous internal web applications from scratch using ExtJS, PHP and SQL that increased the overall efficiency of the department.

### Education

# **University of Surrey**

09/2015 - 07/2019

#### **BSc Computer Science (with year in industry)**

- Graduated with a first class honours
- Completed an industrial placement year at the Royal Surrey County Hospital
- Strived to improve the student experience for others by chairing an intramural university society and volunteering as a listener for Surrey Nightline

### **Bexley Grammar School**

09/2013 - 07/2015

Achieved grades AABBC at A Level

### **Technical Skills**

#### Languages

JavaScript · TypeScript · HTML · CSS · C#

#### Frameworks/Libraries

React · NextJS · Node · NestJS · Express · Sass · Jest

#### Databases/Tools

SQL · MongoDB · Firebase · Git · Jira · Storybook · Heroku · AWS